Indian equity benchmarks rallied on
Wednesday erasing most of Monday's
losses on positive global cues as
optimism grew over a diplomatic solution
to the Middle East conflict.
Both Nifty and Sensex closed 1.6% higher
yesterday.
FIIs net buy stocks worth rupees 666
crore in the cash market. DIIs net sold
stocks worth rupees 569 crore yesterday.
Both S&P 500 and Nasdaq 100 indices
closed at record high
with Bank of America and Morgan Stanley
driving the surge due to better than
expected results.
Asian markets opened higher in trade
today morning following overnight gains
on Wall Street over possibility of a
US-Iran
deal.
Wipro, HDFC Life, HDFC AMC, CRISIL,
Angel One, and Wari Renewables to
announce their fourth quarter FY26
results.
Key results to be announced in post
market hours.
In-line set of results from HDB
Financial Services, ICICI Lombard
General Insurance, whereas weak set of
results from Tejas Networks.
Piramal Enterprises, the company has
entered into an agreement to acquire an
85% stake in Arena Life Sciences for
rupees 176 crore.
It positive revenue Rubicon research
clearly in the medium term.
Agri Sani Hotels, the company has signed
a lease agreement for a 162-room hotel
in Noida. It's arm, Sani Skyline, also
entered into a long-term agreement with
Inca Group to develop an upscale hotel
in a mixed-use project. Positive in
medium term for the company.
Agri Brigade Enterprises, the company
has signed an agreement for an 8.63 acre
development project in East Bengaluru
with a gross development value of rupees
7,200 crore.
Positive in medium term for Brigade
Enterprises.
Agri JHP Infra, the company has received
an a construction contract worth rupees
crore from APCO Infra for miscellaneous
civil works works in Maharashtra. This
is positive in medium term for the
company.
Agri John Cockerill,
the company has received an order worth
rupees 300 crore from JSW Steel quote
for quoted products for the design,
manufacturing, supply, and supervision
of erection and commissioning of a
continuous galvanizing line at its
Kopoli plant. This is positive in medium
term for John Cockerill India.
That's it for today.
Thank you for tuning in. Investment in
securities market are subject to market
risks. Read all the related documents
carefully before investing.